Register of the Okhrana records
Hoover Institution Archives
- XIII. Processing of intelligence (Boxes 106-183, 229-240, 243)
  - f. Index card system (Boxes 173, 229-240, 243)
    - (4) Photographs
      - (a) Prints
        - Stramilov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Strashevich, Sigizmund, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Stringer, Morris, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also John Wade
        - Strokov, Pavel I., circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Struve, Petr Bergardovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Studenik, Petr, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sukhomlin, Vasilii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sukhomlina, Anna, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Asia
        - Sulima, Georgii Stepanovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Surzhitskii, Stefan (Ivan), circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sushchinskii, Mikhail, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sushchinskii, Vladimir, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sutte, Karl, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Svetkovskii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Svezhinskii, Aleksandr Mikhailovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sviatopolk, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Sviderskii, Aleksandr, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Petr Silov
        - Sysoev, Aleksei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tablov, Max, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Tablow
        - Takhtarev, Konstantin, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Takovleva, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Taranov, Konstantin, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tarasov, Boris Favstovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tarasova, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tarasova, Aleksandra, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tarasova, Ol'ga, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tarasova, Vera, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Taratuta, Aron, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Taratuta, Ovsei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Taratuta, Viktor, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tarlo, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Kats
        - Tarshis, Iosif, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Osip Aronovich Piatnitnitskii
        - Taubman, Il'ia Borisovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Teplov, Aleksei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tereshkovich, Iu., circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tetiaev, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Thaer, Ahmed, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tibal'di, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Timashev, Pavel Stepanovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tirimov, Pavel, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tischler, Wilhelm, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tissen, Iogan Gergardovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Titov, Vitalii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tiutchev, Nikolai Sergeevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Tolchenov, Mikhail Alekseevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Tolchenko
        - Toliados, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Toluzakov, Nikolai, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Toporov, Vladimir Viktorovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Trautman, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Trepov, Vasilii Osipov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Trofimenko, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Troianovskii, Boleslav, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Troianskaia, Anna, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Troitskii, Aleksandr, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
        - Troitskii, Vasilii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236M)
          Also Somov
        - Trusevich, Stanislav, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Trushkovskaia, Sof'ia, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Trushkovskii, Ieronim, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsebrikova, M. K., circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsederbaum, Fedor, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsederbaum, Iulii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Martov
        - Tsederbaum, Sergei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Ezhov
        - Tsentura, David, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsentura, Gersh, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsereteli, Mikhail Georgievich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tshchondorisk?, Joseph, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsimmerman, Anatolii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsingovatov, Nikolai, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsingovatova, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsodel, Frants, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Franz Zodel
        - Tsukerman, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Zuckerman
        - Tsvetkov, Grigorii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tsvetkov, Nikolai Grigor'evich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tukmankin, Sergei Petrovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Turchaninov, Pavel Dmitrievich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tverdovskii, Grigorii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Tylitskii, Stanislav, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Tylicki, Tilitskii
        - Tynnikov, Vladimir, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Udalov, Aleksandr Maksimovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Urakina, Rachel, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Usov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Uspenskii, Viktor Petrovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Ustinov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Ustinov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Ustinov, Mikhail Alekseevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Uznadze, Lavrentii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vadimov, Andrei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vainberg(?), Shaika Khamovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vainer, Moisei Abramovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Weiner
        - Vainshtein, Aron, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vainshtein, Semen Lazarevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vallakh, Meer, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Abraham Borisiuk, Maksim Litvinov, Wallach
        - Vanichka, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Varavko, Vasilii Viktorovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also German Savitskii
        - Varenov, Leonid Dmitrievich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Varshavskii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          With Dokhman
        - Varshavskii, Anton, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vartepov, Aleksandr, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vasich, Nikolai Nikolaevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also "Nikolai Voennyi"
        - Vasil'ev, Anton, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vasil'ev, Sergei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - "Vasilii, Grigor'evich,", circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also "Diaden''ka"
        - Vaslavskii, Abram Nakhmanovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vasser, Moisei Iakovlevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vedeniapin, Mikhail Aleksandrovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Veidenfeld, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Veinberg, Abram, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Abraham Weinberg
        - Veinshtok, Viktor, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Veists, Martyn, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Martin Weisz
        - Veiverin, Ivan, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Verigin, Vadim Mikhailovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Versilova, Mariia, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vidmar, Frantsisk, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vikhi or Vikha, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vileon, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vilkov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vil'skii, Ivan, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vil'son, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Wilson
        - Vimba, Arnold, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Arnold Wineba
        - Viniarskii, Lev Eduardovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vinogradov, Viacheslav Kupriianovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Stepa
        - Vinogradov-Bessel', Aleksei Pavlovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vishnevskaia, Ester, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vislitskii, David, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vladimirskii, Mikhail, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vladimov, Grigorii Rubanovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vladzov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vogt, Vladimir, 1908 (Box 236N)
        - Voichinskii, Martyn Ignat'evich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Voinich, Mikhail Leonardovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vol'f, Srul Naftulovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Volianskii, Nikon Ivanovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Volkhovskii, Feliks, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Felix
        - Volkov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Volodia, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Wladislaw
        - Vol'per, Maks, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Max Wolpert
        - Vorovskii, Vatslav, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Wacław Worowski
        - Vovk, Vasilii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vul'fovich, Iulii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vul'fson, Vigdor, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Vul'pe, Ivan, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Walk, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Wasiutynski, Andrew, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Weber, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Werbaough, Moise, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
          Also Werbach?
        - Werner, Friedrich Karl, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Winkler, Ernest, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Wojciechowski, Stanisław, 1893 (Box 236N)
          Also Stanislav Vaitsekhovskii
        - Wraag, Wasil Michaelovitz, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236N)
        - Yehudda, Shaiak, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zafiridi, Aleksandr, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also Grekov
        - Zaitsev, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zaitsev, Grigorii Stepanovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zaitseva, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zakharchenko, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zakhar'ev, Iarchuk Khaim, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zakharov, Denis Efimovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zakras, Andrei, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zalevskii, Feofil, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zalmanov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zamukhovskii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zapol'skii, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also Dovnar
        - Zaslavskaia, Mariia, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zavadskii, Aleksandr Antonovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zbarskii, Iakov Feliksovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zborovskii, Saul Shlemovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zeia, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zeitkin, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zelenskii, Evgenii Osipovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zelich?, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zel'tser, Anton, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zemliachka, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zenzinov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zeziulenskii, Girsh (Nikolai), circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also "Bogdan"
        - Zhelikhovskaia, Ol'ga, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also Vinogradova
        - Zherkov-Zherchenko, Tikhon, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zheronimius, Bella, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also Geronimus
        - Zhilin, Ivan Iakovlevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zhitlovskii, Khaim, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Includes Avram and Shaia Zhitlovskii
        - Zhnudskii, Vatslav, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zhukaev, Salangkeri (Nikolai) Asakhmetovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zhuravlev, Petr Petrovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also Vasilii Beziuk
        - Zhurovskii, Cheslav-Feliks Ignat'evich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zick, Michael Semenowitz, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zommerfel'd, Vladislav Iakovlevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also "Martynov"
        - Zuikov, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
        - Zverin, Aron Isaakovich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
          Also Zverev
        - Zyrulnik, Levi Nosolevich, circa 1883-1917 (Box 236O)
      - (b) Glass negatives (Boxes 238-240)
      - (c) Police identity reports
        Downloadable PDF Index of Police Identity Reports
        Police Identity Reports Index
        - Handwritten report, 1913 July 31 (Box 243)
          "'Signalement' description of unknown person."
        - Abachidzé, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Abachidzé, Alexandre, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Abdreef, Lydia, 1918 (Box 243)
        - Abrahamoff, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Agafonoff, Talérian, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Akhmatoff, Jean, 1914 February 10 (Box 243)
        - Alexinsky, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Andreff, Georges, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Arefieff, 1919 (Box 243)
        - Auerbach, Vladimir, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Babroff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Balabanoff, Angelique, 1914 March 7 (Box 243)
        - Barthold, Boris, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Barthold, Boris, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bass, Guillet, 1914 March 4 (Box 243)
        - Beckermann, 1913 August 13 (Box 243)
        - Beloussoff, Alexandre, 1913 August 1 (Box 243)
        - Beloussoff, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Beloussoff, Valentine, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Benson, Nathan, 1916 February 14 (Box 243)
        - Berezine, Victor, 1913 August 1 (Box 243)
        - Berlinoff, Auguste, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bernatsky, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Berzine, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Berzine, Jean, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
          Letter from J. Berzine to Madame
        - Bettinkoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bezuck, Yourauleff, 1913 August (Box 243)
        - Bichantropp, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Blank index card, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Blumenfeld, Amelie, 1913 August (Box 243)
        - Blumenfeld, Joseph, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Blumental, Adolphe, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bogatski, Henri, 1913 September 25 (Box 243)
        - Bogazski, Henri, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bogdanoff, 1913 August (Box 243)
        - Borissoff, 1913 August (Box 243)
        - Borissoff, Terye, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Bornemann, Vladimir, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bornstein, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Boulgakoff, Georges, 1912 (Box 243)
        - Bourtzeff, Vladimir, 1913 August 1 (Box 243)
        - Boutilkine, Jean, 1913 August 1 (Box 243)
        - Boyasky, Harry, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Brodsky, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Brodsky, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
          Sheet of paper with list of relations
        - Brodsky, Sophie, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Broon, Victor, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Brozgol, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Bykoff, Alexis, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Chagiakhmetoff, Tslam, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Chagiakhmetoff, Tslam, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Chalitte, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Chalitte, Molf, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Chenisse, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Chmaisnok, Moise, 1913 August 19 (Box 243)
        - Choulik, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Dakar, Auguste, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Davidoff, Maria, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Debreyne, Charles, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Depohl, Jules, Gustave, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Desaube, Georges, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Djeaparidse Ivanovsky, Tarina, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Dobrovolsky, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Dolyenko, Anna, 1913 July 26 (Box 243)
        - Dory, 1914 March 6 (Box 243)
        - Efroussi, Sophie, 1913 August (Box 243)
        - Eichembaum, Tsevolade, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Eitchinsky, Alexandre, 1914 January 15 (Box 243)
        - Elkine, 1913 August (Box 243)
        - Erofeieff, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Eroffeef, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Fabricantoff, Julia, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Faynsilberg, Paul, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Federoff, Victor, 1913 July 11 (Box 243)
        - Fedoroff, Jean Henry, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Fedoroff, Olga, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Fedoroff, Ossipe, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Figner, Vera, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Finkelberg, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Flabukaul, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Foudameusky, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Frielich, Jacques, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Frielich, Jacques, 1913 July 12 (Box 243)
        - Galperine, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Gambachidze, Basile, 1914 March 24 (Box 243)
        - Geiger, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Glik, Naoum, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Glotoff, Jacques, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Glukmann, 1913 July 23 (Box 243)
        - Goguelia, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Goldstein, Maurice, 1910 (Box 243)
        - Gorfinkel, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Gorodetski, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Gotz, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
          Note to 'Chere Madame' from 'V. Gotz'
        - Gotz, Vera, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Gouliaeff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Gredinger, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Gretchneff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Gribine, 1912 (Box 243)
        - Guedrine, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Guessesberg, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Guessesberg, Zarehis, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Guinsberg, 1913 August 19 (Box 243)
        - Haeprezath, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Handwritten report, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
          Handwritten report, title reads: "Signalemente"
        - Herzenstein, Judas Wolf, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Hichmann, Anatole, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Holstein, Vladimir, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Hzikowsky, Elias, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Ignatin, Muzil, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Ivanoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Ivanoff, Sophie, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Jakinoff, Michel, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Jakowlewieff, Cain, 1913 August 13 (Box 243)
        - Jasfroboff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Jeanne, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Jeanne, Pierre, Serge, Albert, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Joukowski, Alexandre, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kabanoff, Antoine, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kacendenbagvey, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kadomtzeff, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kalian, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Karaline, Apollon, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Karassouloff, Helene, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Karassouloff, Olga, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Karlstein, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Karpovitch, Pierre, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kasatchenko, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Katcharovsky, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Khoudadoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Khoudadoff, Marie, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Khoudadoff, Vladimir, 1914 August (Box 243)
        - Kirischeck, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kissme, Alexandre, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kissme, Alexandre, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Klapina, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
          Handwritten note to Mlle Klapina from Julie.
        - Kleibass, Edouard, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Klepikoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kletovsky, Edouard, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Klimoff, Nathalie, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kobylansky, Ladislav, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kobylinsky, Ladyslas, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kogan, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kolegaeff, 1912 (Box 243)
        - Kolossoff, Eugene, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Komirsky, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Konstantinoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kopelova, Nathalie, 1913 August 19 (Box 243)
        - Korsouvsky, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kosloff, Jacques, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kosmodamiansky, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kosowsky, Michel, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kotik, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kotrotkoff, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Koulikovsky, Pierre, 1911 (Box 243)
        - Koulischer, Jacob, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Koumeny, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kourisko, Michel, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kouzmine, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kravetz, Jean, 1913 August 13 (Box 243)
        - Kriegel Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kronstaloff, Mazar, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Kropolkine, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kroul, Jacob, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Kurland, Abraham, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Laille, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Landy, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Laouer, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Lapatine, Kevolad, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Lapine, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Lazareff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Lebensbaum, Edouard, 1914 February 10 (Box 243)
        - Leonovitch, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Leonovitch, Marie, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Leonowitch, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Lesaulvier, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Letchtinki, David, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Lezinnes, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Ligsky, Constantin, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Loubarsky, Vera, 1914 February 26 (Box 243)
        - Lunovziarsky, Valerian, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Makovhime, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Maleeff, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Maltzeff, Jean, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Malysceff, Alexandre, 1913 September 25 (Box 243)
        - Man leaning back against a rock face, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Markach, Nina, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Martinson, Edouard, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Martmoff, Jean, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Maurice, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Mazurenko, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Medwed, Michel, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Meerowitch, Leo, 1914 February 10 (Box 243)
        - Meissmer, Ferdinand, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Meitousse, Anna, 1909 July 31 (Box 243)
        - Metalnikoff, Ivanoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Meteh, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Minor, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Miroliouboff, Victor, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Moiche, Fiskinel, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Moiisseenko, Boris, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Moiisseenko, Nicolas, Serge, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Moisenko, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Monassovitch, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Mousenko, Serge, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Moyseff, Nadine, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Mychkine, Basile, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Nassonoff, Olga, circa 1883-1917 (Box 243)
        - Natanson, Marc, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Nesseriantz, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Neymeyanoff, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Nikitin, 1913 (Box 243)
        - Nikolaeff, 1912 (Box 243)
        - Nikolaeff, Michel, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 1, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 2, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 3, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 4, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 5, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 6, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 7, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 8, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 9, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 10, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 11, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 12, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 13, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 14, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 15, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 17, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 18, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 20, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 28, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 29, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 31, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 36, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 37, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 39, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 43, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 44, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 45, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 46, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 47, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 48, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 49, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 50, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 51, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 52, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 53, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 55, Aleksai Kanashev, 1909 (Box 243)
        - No. 56, femme de Kolary, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 59, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 60, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 61, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 62, 1913 (Box 243)
        - [No. 62?], 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 63, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 64, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 65, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 66, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 67, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 68, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 69, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 70, 1913 (Box 243)
        - No. 71, 1913 (Box 243)